The ancient well shelled
mariners sadly met their fate.
Hey everyone. Welcome back to my channel.
Today I want to talk about the
Cambrin period. 500 million years ago,
the armored set ruled the seas.
These animals secreted a mineral paste
that hardened into protective shells.
Some of these shells were shaped
like Rams heads or eagles wings.
Others were shaped like champagne
flutes, studded with dagger sharp spines.
But by the Devonian period,
70 million years later,
most of these animals were extinct.
They were victims of theft and their own
extravagant ways. That's all for today.
I hope you enjoyed this video. If
you did, please like and subscribe.
Thanks for watching.